Guide to the Leonard Solomon Silk papers, 1929-1995 and undated, bulk 1950-1985 RL.01187
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession 6096, 1933-1985, and undated, 86 boxes
  - Serial Publications (Box 45)
    - Graduate School of Business, University of Chicago, selected
      - No. 2, Davidson, S., The Meaning Depreciation. (Box 45)
      - No. 3, Stigler, G. J., The Intellectual and the Market Place. (Box 45)
      - No. 4, Weber, A. R., Retaining the Unemployed. (Box 45)
      - No. 5, Aldrich, C. K., Executive Behavior. (Box 45)
      - No. 7, Stigler, G. J., and P. A. Samuelson, A Dialogue on the Proper Economic Role of the State. (Box 45)
      - No. 8, Shultz, G. P., Strikes: The Private Stake and the Public Interest. (Box 45)
      - No. 9, Whisler, T. L., Executives and Their Jobs - The Changing Organizational Structure. (Box 45)
      - No. 11, Yntema, T. O. Education - Some Neglected Opportunities. (Box 45)
      - No. 12, Fackler, W. D. Federal Spending as an Economic Stabilizer. (Box 45)
      - No. 13, Stigler, G. J. The Tactics of Economic Reform. (Box 45)
      - No. 14, Becker, S. W. The Innovative Organization. (Box 45)
      - No. 15, Zarnowitz, V., Forecasting Business Conditions: a Critical View. (Box 45)
      - No. 16, Famu, E. F., Random Walks in Stock Market Prices. (Box 45)
      - No. 17, Johnson, H. G., American in the World Economy - The Decade Ahead. (Box 45)
      - No. 18, Brozen, Y., Automation and Jobs. (Box 45)
      - No. 19, Jeuck, J. E., Marketing Policy: Another View of the Forest. (Box 45)
      - No. 20, Lorie, J. H., Current Controversies on the Stock Market. (Box 45)
      - No. 21, Weber, A. R., Labor Lessons, Notes from Europe. (Box 45)
      - No. 22 Schultz, G. P., and R. Z. Aliber, Guidelines, Informal Controls, and the Market Place. (Box 45)
      - No. 23, Miller, M. H. and D. Orr, Mathematical Models for Financial Management. (Box 45)
      - No. 24, Davidson, S. The Meaning of Business Income: An International Comparison. (Box 45)
      - No. 25, Ture, N. B., The New Economics: Stabilizing Tax Policy. (Box 45)
      - No. 26, Wrapp, H. E. Good Managers Don't Make Policy Decisions. (Box 45)
      - No. 27, Lorie, J. H., Government and Advertising: The Heavy Hand of Benevolence. (Box 45)
      - No. 28, Fackler, W. D., The Long View and The Short. (Box 45)
      - No. 29, Hoffman, R. Are People Really Important in Business. (Box 45)
      - No. 31, Dreze, J. The American Presence in Europe. (Box 45)
    - Korea, New Community Movement - Better Tomorrow Through Cooperative Efforts, Policy Series, No. 4, June 1972 (Box 45)
    - Malmgren, H. B. Trade for Development, Overseas Development Council Monograph Number Four, Washington, D.C. 1971 (Box 45)
    - University of Waterloo, The Faculty Arts, Department of Economics, Waterloo, Ontario
      - Waterloo Economic Series No. 35, Weintraub, S. and H. Habibagahi, Money Supplies a Price, Neutral and Output, Sasual, March 1971 (Box 45)
      - Waterloo Economic Series No. 37, Wallich, H. and S. Weintraub, A Tax Based Incomes Policy, April 1971 (Box 45)
    - West Virginia University, Kanawha Valley Graduate Center series. Silk, Leonard, The Economics of the Johnson Administration, Professional Development Lectures, Vol 1, No. 1, August 1968 (Box 45)
  - Speeches, Addresses, Statements (Box 45)
    - Aaron, H., Inventory of Existing Tax Incentives, Federal Tax Institute of America Symposium, November 21-21, 1969, 18 pages (Box 45)
    - Abel, I. W., Chairman AFL-CIO Economics Policy Committee and President of the United Steelworkers of America, Statement to the Joint Economic Committee of the Congress on the Mid-Year Economic Review, August 14, 1974, 12 pages mimeograph (Box 45)
    - Ackley, G., Statement Before the Committee on the Budget, United States Senate, August 14, 1974. 15 pages mimeograph (Box 45)
    - Statement on Behalf of the American Retail Federation Before the Committee on Ways and Means, U.S. house of Representatives.. May 18, 1970. pp. 1-15 (Box 45)
    - Adams, A. V., Toward Fair Employment and the EEOC. King Edward Hotel, Toronto, Canada, December 12, 1972, 20 pages mimeo (Box 45)
    - Adelman, M. A., Coping with Oil Cartel. Address to National Press Club, Washing, D.C., May 9. 8 pages xerox (Box 45)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council, Statement on the National Economy, Washington, D.C., May 12, 1970, 4 pages mimeo (Box 45)
    - Agnelli, G., The Changing World Scene and the International Automotive Industry. Society of Automotive Engineers, Annual Dinner Banquet, January 12, 1972. 14 pages (Box 45)
    - Anderson, E. E. Corporation Organization with its Social, Political and Economic Implications, Address given October 19, 1961, New York. Printed (Box 45)
    - Altman, E. I., Railroad Bankruptcy Propensity, American Finance Association Meeting, Detroit, Michigan, December 28, 1970, 29 pages mimeo (Box 45)
    - Bell, E. V. A Change of Eras, Presented Before the Copper and Brass Research Association, Virginia, May 17, 1960 (Box 45)
    - The Economic Outlook on the New Frontier, Presented before the Wine and Spirits Wholesalers of America, Inc., Hawaii, April 19, 1961, printed (Box 45)
    - Bergsten, F. C., Future Directions for U.S. Trade, Royal York Hotel, Toronto, Canada, December 29, 1972, 20 pages mimeo (Box 45)
    - Statement to Subcommittee on International Finance of the House Banking and Currency Committee, March 7, 1973. 11 pages photocopy, annotated (Box 45)
    - Bergsten, F. C., The U.S. Position in the World Economy of the 1970s. Statement before the Subcommittee on International Finance of the Committee on the Banking and Currency, December 6, 1973. 13 pages xerox (Box 45)
    - Billings, B. Internal and External Effects of United States Commercial Policy, Toronto, Canada, December 27, 1972, 25 pages xerox (Box 45)
    - Boyd, H., Statement before the Senate Commerce Committee, Seattle, Washington, April 19, 1971, Proposed Legislation to Preserve the El Paso-Pacific Northwest merger. 26 page, in grey folder (Box 45)
  - Speeches (Box 46)
    - Brimmer, A. F., The Black Banks - An Assessment of Performance and Prospects, Before a Joint Session of the 1970 Annual Meeting of the American Finance Association and The American Economic Association, Detroit, Michigan, December 28, 1970, 50 pages xerox (Box 46)
    - Education, Income, and Wealth Accumulation in the Negro Community. Commencement Address, Birmingham, Alabama, May 28, 1970. 12 pages (Box 46)
    - Import Controls and Domestic Inflation. University of Maryland, November 11, 1970, 16 pages mimeo (Box 46)
    - Multinational Banks and the Management of Monetary Policy, December 28-30, 1972. Toronto, Canada, Royal York Hotel, 71 pages xerox (Box 46)
    - Burns, A. F., Statement before the Committee on ways and Means, House of Representatives, January 30, 1975. 9 pages mimeo (Box 46)
    - Busschau, W.J., The Case Against Demonetization of Gold, International Monetary Symposium, Carlton Hotel, October 2, 1973, 10 pages mimeo, annotated (Box 46)
    - Chandler, A. D., Jr., The Role of Business in the United States - An Historical Survey, Boston, MA, March 28-29, 1968. 34 pages mimeo (Box 46)
    - Clague, C. Legal Strategies for Dealing with Heroin Addiction, Royal York Hotel, Toronto, Canada, December 29, 1972, 20 pages mimeo (Box 46)
    - Connally, J. B. Remarks at the 59th Annual Convention, Investment Bankers Association of America, Florida, December 2, 1970, 17 pages photocopy (Box 46)
    - Conrad, A. H. Unemployment in a Growing Economy: The U.S. Case. A program for Balanced Regional Growth. University of Edinburgh, April 19, 1962. 18 pages (Box 46)
    - Cook, G. B. The Central Market System: Putting the markets to Work for the Investor, March 15, 1973, Americana Hotel, New York, 20 pages mimeo (Box 46)
    - Cooper, R. N. The Future of the Dollar, January 306, 1973. Conference on the International Monetary Problem Ditchley Park, 24 pages, incomplete, mimeo (Box 46)
    - D'Estaing, C. G. The New World Economic Order, 2 copies, October 28, 1975. 15 pages (Box 46)
    - French Foreign Policy and Defense, November 12, 1975, 10 pages (Box 46)
    - Economic Summit Meeting at Rambouillet. November 12, 1975, 5 pages (Box 46)
    - De Seynes, P., The United National and the Changing World Economy. March 8, 1973, Chicago, 11 pages mimeo (Box 46)
    - Dinner Discussion, Various Speakers, undated, 25 pages xerox (Box 46)
    - Dolde, W., and J. Tobin, Wealth, Liquidity and Consumption, June 20-22, 1971 xerox copy (Box 46)
    - Eckstein, O. The Economic Outlook: A Trip Through The Chamber of Horrors. Before the International Purchasing Conference of the National Association of Purchasing Management, May 20, 1970. Boston, 10 pages printed (Box 46)
    - A Plethora of Lessons from the Recent Expansion. Paper prepared for the Annual Meeting of the American Economic Association, 8 pages, mimeo, annotated (Box 46)
    - The U.S. Economy in 1973-1974 and Some Contingencies. Paper to be presented to the American Finance Association, Toronto, Canad, December 29, 1972. 10 pages mimeo (Box 46)
    - Enders, T. O., Statement before the Joint Economic Committee, November 29, 1974. 17 pages mimeo (Box 46)
    - Englert, J. Carlino, International Financial Aspects of the Energy Crisis, February 1974, Working Paper No. 17 to be presented to the U.S. Senate Committee on Commerce. Printed (Box 46)
    - Excerpts for the Presentation of Alan Greenspan, President of Townsend-Greenspan and Co., Economic and Financial Outlook, American Finance Association, New Orleans, December 28, 1971, 2 pages xerox (Box 46)
    - Excerpts from the President's Speech on Economy, June 17, 1970. 9 pages mimeo (Box 46)
    - Fand, David I. Some Observations on Current Stabilization Policy, lecture presented at Western Michigan University, January 20, 1971. 21 pages mimeo (Box 46)
    - Farrar, D., hearing Conducted by Subcommittee on Securities Committee on Banking, April 21, 1972. 18 pages typed (Box 46)
    - Fellner, W., Trends in the Activities Generating Technological Progress. To be presented on December 29, American Economic Association. 4 pages (Box 46)
    - Fowler, H. H. Partner, Cleveland, Ohio, January 25, 1972. 17 pages (Box 46)
    - Remarks before the Sixth International Financial Business Outlook Conference, Frankfurt, Germany, October 28, 1975, 21 pages mimeo (Box 46)
    - Freeman, R. B., Decline of Labor Market Discrimination and Economic Analysis. Royal York Hotel, Toronto, Canada, December 28, 1972. 16 pages mimeo (Box 46)
    - Galbraith, J. K. Power and the Useful Economists, December 30, 1972. Royal York Hotel, Toronto, Canada. 20 pafes xerox (Box 46)
    - Galledo, E. B., Fiscal and Monetary Policies to Stabilize Total Demand. February 17, 1972, 4 pages (Box 46)
    - Gardener, R. N., The New U.S. Trade Bill and the Prospects for European-American Economic Relations, July 10, 1972. 12 pages mimeo (Box 46)
    - Testimony to the Subcommittee on International Economics of the Joint Economic Committee of the United States Congress, December 13, 1973. 11 pages mimeo (Box 46)
    - Gardner, R. N., The Trade Reform Bill as an Instrument of Foreign Economic Policy. New York, November 14, 1973, 13 pages mimeo (Box 46)
    - Gellman, A. J., Economic Regulation and Innovative Performance in Surface Transportation. Prepared for the Conference on Technological Change in the Regulated Industries, Washington, D.C. February 6-7, 1969. 65 pages mimeo. 2 copies (Box 46)
    - Gideonse, H. D., The Economic Foreign Policy of the United States, Fiftieth Anniversary Commemoration Lectures, Cairo 1953. printed (Box 46)
    - Gordon, S., Today's Apocalypses and Yesterday's, December 28-30, 1972. Four Seasons Hotel, Toronto, Canada, 9 pages xerox (Box 46)
    - Green, E. W., Inflation: Why and What Next? Presented at FSUC Conference on Inflation, October 10, 1973. 7 pages xerox (Box 46)
    - Green, G. D., The Economic Impact of the Stock Market Boom and Crash of 1929, June 22, 1971. 47 pages xerox (Box 46)
    - Greenhouse, S. M. Gaps in Government Economic Approaches: Future Requirements, December 28-30, 1972. Royal Oak Hotel, Toronto, Canada, 7 pages xerox (Box 46)
    - Haberler, G. The Future of the International Monetary System and the Convertibility of the Dollar. January 6, 1973. Universite du Quebec, Montreal, 22 pages, mimeograph (Box 46)
    - Haughton, D. J., Chairman of the Board, National Press Club, Washington, D.C. June 28, 1971. 5 pages mimeograph (Box 46)
    - H. E. Sabah Al-Ahmad Al-Jaber Al-Sabah, Minister of Foreign Affairs of the the State of Kuwait... New York, April 16, 1974. 22 pages mimeo (Box 46)
    - Heller, W. W., The Battle Against U.S. Inflation, Remarks before the International Monetary Conference of the American Bankers Association, Hot Springs, Virginia, May 19, 1970. 9 pages (Box 46)
    - Corrected transcript of Remarks on President Nixon's New Economic Policy, Before the Joint Economic Committee, August 19, 1971. 16 pages mimeo (Box 46)
    - Economic Growth and the Quality and Equality of Life. Franklin Lecture, Auburn University, Revised, September 1, 1972, 18 pages (Box 46)
    - Statement before the Joint Economic Committee, August 1, 1974. 12 pages mimeo (Box 46)
  - Speeches (Box 47)
    - Hirschleifer, J., Where are we in the Theory of Information? December 28-20, 1972. Royal York Hotel, Toronto, Canada. 20 pages xerox (Box 47)
    - Holton, R. H., Business and Government, March 28-29, 1968. Boston, Mass, 18 pages mimeo (Box 47)
    - Homer, S., Structural Changes in the American Bond Market. London, June 3, 1970. 19 pages mimeo (Box 47)
    - Jackson, H. M., Our National Priority: Jobs, Address to the Economic club of New York, May 4, 1971. 12 pages mimeo (Box 47)
    - Javits, J. K., The Need for Economic Planning, Rosslyn, Va. November 13, 1975. 1 page (Box 47)
    - Johnson, D. G., The Impact of Free Trade on North American Agriculture. Paper prepared for joint session of the American Economic Association and the American Agricultural Economic Association, Toronto, December 29, 1972 (Box 47)
    - Johnson, H. G., The Keynesian Revolution and the Monetarist Counter Revolution. 83rd Annual Meeting of the American Economic Association, Detroit, December 28, 1970. 17 pages mimeo. 2 copies (Box 47)
    - Jones, R. H., Capital Requirements of Business, 1974-1975. Testimony to Subcommittee on Economic Growth, May 8, 1974. Printed (Box 47)
    - Kagan, S., The Current Economic Situation. Address given before IBM Executives in New Selhi, February 26, 1975. 13 pages (Box 47)
    - Kahn, R., The International Monetary System, December 28-30, 1972. Four Season Hotel, Toronto, 18 pages xerox (Box 47)
    - Kaufman, H., The Cyclical and Secular Trends of Interest Rates. Waldorf-Astoria, New York, November 21, 1975. 29 pages multilith (Box 47)
    - The Prospects for Interest Rates and Liquidity. Address before the Investment and Property Studies Conference, London, October 28, 1970. 15 pages multilith (Box 47)
    - Kendall, D. M., Statement of behalf of the Emergency Committee for American Trade before the Committee on Ways and Means. May 18, 1970. 23 pages (Box 47)
    - Kissinger, H. A., Transcript of a news conference given by Dr. Kissinger on June 12, 1972 in Tokyo. 6 pages ditto (Box 47)
    - Klaman, S. B., The 1970 Outlook for Housing and Mortgage Finance. New York, December 29, 1969. 5 pages mimeo (Box 47)
    - Kleinman, D. T., A Plan to Utilize the Excess Capital Reserves of the Oil Producing Countries to Assist the Economic Development of the Third World. Paris, May 8, 1974. 16 pages (Box 47)
    - Krause, W., UNCTAD III: Implications for Multinational Enterprise. Toronto, December 29, 1972. 19 pages xerox (Box 47)
    - Krueger, R. B., Statement to the Ad Hoc Select Committee on Outer Continental Shelf ... November 14, 1975. 20 pages mimeo (Box 47)
    - Kuh, E., Econometric Models -- Is a New Age Dawning? For Presentation to American Economics Association, December 30, 1964. 14 pages typescript (Box 47)
    - Leontief, W., Statement before the Joint Economic Committee 22 page, mimeograph (Box 47)
    - Structure of the World Economy - Outline of a Simple Input-Output Formulation. Nobel Lecture, December 11, 1973, 29 pages mimeograph (Box 47)
    - Levine, I. M., A Strategy for White Ethnic America. Philadelphia June 1968, 14 pages ditto (Box 47)
    - Levy, Walter J. An Action Program for U.S. Energy Policy During the Seventies. Address for Presentation at a General Session American Petroleum Institute, Chicago, November 13-14, 1972. 15 pages xerox (Box 47)
    - Lewis, R. G., Expanding Concessional Sales of U.S. Farm Commodities, Before 15th Annual Grain Marketing Seminar, August 6 and 7, 1969. 11 pages mimeograph (Box 47)
    - Longman, K. A., Advertising and Attitude Research: Unfair to Consumers? Delivered to the Second Annual Symposium, University of Rhode Island, April 1968, 13 pages (Box 47)
    - How to Spot and Use a Psychographic. Delivered to the American Marketing Association, Atlanta, Georgia, June 17, 1969, 12 pages (Box 47)
    - What do you Mean - Product Design? Presented to the 31st National Meeting, Operations Research Society, New York, June 2, 1967. 16 pages (Box 47)
    - McCracken, P. W., Statement before the Joint Economic Committee, July 20, 1970. 35 pages mimeo (Box 47)
    - Maier, Cornell C., Regarding Development in Jamaica. Statement, Oakland, California. June 17, 1974. 6 pages (Box 47)
    - Malott, R. H., Testimony of FMC Corporation, July 23, 1975. 13 pages (Box 47)
    - Mansfield, M., Statement A Proposal for a New Approach on Economic Foresight, April 11, 1974 (Box 47)
    - Marris, S., The Burgenstock Communique: A Critical Examination of the Case for Limited Exchange Rate Flexibility. September 18, 1969, 55 pages (Box 47)
    - Matter, A., A European View of the Future of Gold. undated n.p., 26 pages xerox (Box 47)
    - Meiselman, D., Monetary Policy and Consumer Expenditures: The Historical Evidence. June 20-22, 1971. Preliminary copy, 53 pages. Final copy, 33 pages, mimeo (Box 47)
    - Statement to Joint Hearings...Policy of the House Banking and Currency Committee. July 17, 1975. 12 pages photocopy (Box 47)
    - Worldwide Inflation: A Monetarist View. Washington, D.C. May 6, 1974. 40 pages, mimeo (Box 47)
    - Mena, A. O. Inaugural Address, Buenos Aires, March 1, 1971. 11 pages photocopy (Box 47)
    - Meyer, J., Draft, Introductory Remarks for AEA December Meeting, undated 5 pages xerox (Box 47)
    - Mitchell, G. W., Statement before the Committee on Banking ... October 3, 1973. 15 pages photocopy (Box 47)
    - Moran, W. T., Parameters of Profitability. September 15, 1972. 16 pages photocopy (Box 47)
    - Ten Score Years or Three Lifetimes Later - Consumer Non-Durables, What is Happening? Waldorf-Astoria, New York, September 16, 1975. 37 pages mimeograph (Box 47)
    - Monsen, R. J., Is the Business Image Changing? March 28-29, 1968, Boston, Mass 26 pages mimeo (Box 47)
    - Morgens, H., Government and Private Enterprise, A Search for Balance. New York, November 7, 1975. 9 pages multilith (Box 47)
    - Muller-Thym, B. J., The Taxonomy of Business, March 28-29, 1968, Brookline, MA. 56 pages mimeo (Box 47)
    - Nathan, R. R., Testimony on Petroleum Pricing ... July 10, 1975. 14 pages (Box 47)
    - Needham, J. J., The Cost of Economic Growth, September 9, 1974. 18 pages mimeograph, 3 copies (Box 47)
    - Noll, R. G., Broadcast Content and Government Policy. April 27, 1970. 24 pages (Box 47)
    - Okun, A. M. Comments on General Economic Conditions and National Elections, Royal York Hotel, Toronto, December 28, 1972. 13 pages, mimeograph, 2 copies (Box 47)
    - Inflation: The Problems and Prospects Before US. New York, November 10, 1969. 32 pages mimeo (Box 47)
    - O'Leary, J. J., The Outlook for General Business Activity and the Money and Capital Markets, July 23, 1970. Houston, 31 pages, mimeo (Box 47)
    - Oweiss, I., Petro Money and the International Monetary System. Malibu, CA, May 1974. 11 pages (Box 47)
    - Petro Money: Problems and Prospects. New York, March 1974, 12 pages, mimeo, annotated (Box 47)
  - Speeches (Box 48)
    - Pechman, J. A., International Trends in the Distribution of Tax Burdens: Implications for Tax Policy. England, October 30, 1973. 19 pages mimeo (Box 48)
    - Taxation, Investment and Growth. June 25, 1975. 12 pages xerox (Box 48)
    - Perkins, D. H., Plans and Their Implementation in the People's Republic of China. December 28-30, 1972. Royal York Hotel, Toronto, Canada, 19 pages, xerox (Box 48)
    - Perry, G. L., Statement before the Congress... July 24, 1975. 5 pages, xerox (Box 48)
    - Raffety, J., An Analysis of the Effects of Medicare on Discretionary Hospital Use. December 28-30, 1972. Royal York Hotel, Toronto, Canada, 20 pages, xerox (Box 48)
    - Revelle, R., Society and Technology in the Present and Future World, Expanded Summary of Fourth Lecture, 5 pages (Box 48)
    - Rosow, J. M., The Work Ethic and Welfare Reform, December 28-30, 1972. King Edward Hotel, Toronto, Canada, 14 pages, xerox (Box 48)
    - Ruml, B., National Fiscal Policy, Princeton University, May 2, 1950, 13 pages xerox (Box 48)
    - Salmond, F., Address to the Students of the Julliard School of Music at Convocation, September 17, 1948. Printed, autographed by author (Box 48)
    - Schell, O. H., New York State Moreland Act Commission on the Urban Development Corporation and Other State Financing Agencies. October 14, 1975, 9 pages xerox. Added to Above, opening statements, 21 pages, xerox (Box 48)
    - Schnittker, J. A., Prospects for Freer Economic Trade. Royal York Hotel, Toronto, Canada, December 29, 1972. 14 pages mimeo (Box 48)
    - Schott, F. H., Persistent Inflation and the Path of Its Potential Progression. The Ticket Club, Toronto, Canada, March 15, 1974. 12 pages, annotated (Box 48)
    - Schultze, C. L., Governmental and Public Data Needs, undated AEA Meeting, 18 pages mimeo (Box 48)
    - Selucky, R., Marxism and Self Management. Cornell University, 1973, 22 pages mimeo (Box 48)
    - Silk, Leonard S.
      - Business Forecasting: Is It Really Getting Any Better? Addressed before the Sixth Annual Midwest Conference of the American Statistical Association and the Chicago Association of Commerce and Industry, March 26, 1959, 11 pages photocopy (Box 48)
      - Data Needs of Private Enterprises. Paper to be presented before the 82nd Annual Meeting of the American Economic Association, New York, December 29, 1969. Two Copies. One 15 pages, mimeo, annotated, and another 3 pages typescript (Box 48)
      - The Goals of Business Education. Address to the Council for Professional Education for Business, MA, December 27, 1963. 15 pages mimeo (Box 48)
      - Good Sense and Bad Data, Address to the Market Research Council, New York, December 15, 1972. 12 pages mimeo (Box 48)
      - The Research Revolution and Public Policy. American Association for the Advancement of Science,127th Meeting, December 29, 1960. 18 pages mimeo (Box 48)
      - The Social Impact of Economic Change in the 1970s. Annual Meeting of the Paperboard Packing Council, Drake Hotel, Chicago, March 25, 1970. 12 pages (Box 48)
      - What do we Mean by Commitment? Commencement address, Southeastern Massachusetts Technological Institute, June 21, 1967. 11 pages xerox (Box 48)
    - Simon, W.E., Statement before the Joint Economic Committee, November 7, 1975 (Box 48)
    - Singer, E. M., Industrial Organization: Price Models and the Public Policy, December 28, 1969. 31 pages multilith (Box 48)
    - Solomon, R., The Oil Price Impact on the International Monetary System. Address before the 1974 International Accounting Conference, New York, May 13, 1974. 15 pages (Box 48)